Brian Kim

brianshkim25@gmail.com 213-258-0488 <u>Linkedin</u> <u>Github</u> Portfolio

SKILLS Javascript, Python, React, Redux, Node.js, Flask, HTML5, CSS3, Docker, Socket.io, Express.js, Postgresql, SQLAlchemy, Alembic

CERTIFICATIONS CompTIA A+, Security+ and Network+ (currently working on CCNA)

PROJECTS

Ioniq (Javascript, Python, React, Redux, Node.js, HTML5, Flask, PostgreSQL, SQLAlchemy and CSS3)

Live Site | Github A fullstack single-page Discord clone where users can join Server and Channels, and see users online while chatting

- Designed an application based webUI that focuses on minimalistic style and an intuitive chatting experience.
- Deployed several React components with websockets on one page to provide a seamless user experience
- Interweaved logic that rendered different components at different times (conditional rendering) for specific uses.

Spectral Waves (Javascript, React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Express, and AWS s3)

Live Site | Github

- A fullstack single-page SoundCloud clone where users can upload their own music, and make their own playlists.
 - Leveraged a file server to provide users with their personal experience in making their own music profiles.
 - Created UI that renders the user's playlists and songs on the fly
 - Stylized a unique UI that compares to SoundCloud

AlphaHood (Javascript, Python, React, Redux, HTML5, Flask, PostgreSQL, SQLAlchemy and CSS3)

Live Site | Github

- A fullstack Robinhood clone that simulates the selling and buying of stocks
 - Cooperated with multiple developers to create a website that simulates stock prices and user portfolios
 - Developed logic that help track user portfolios as they bought individual stocks and sold them

EXPERIENCE

Golden State Seafood/Pacific Fresh Fish Company, Assistant to the Operations Manager Los Angeles, CA Feb 2018-November 2020

- Supervised and optimized routes for 7-9 delivery drivers
- Tracked inventory as they were sold and delivered to customers using custom company software
- Handled troubleshooting and maintenance of company computers

G & H Medical Transportation, Assistant Dispatcher Glendale, CA

October 2016-March 2017

- Mobilized the transporting of patients to their doctors and crucial medical appointments
- Optimized routing of drivers to destinations to pick up additional patient trips

EDUCATION

App Academy Online Remote

Feb 2022-July 2022

 1000 hrs of hands-on practical software engineer skills including object-oriented programming (OOP), data structure algorithms, paired programming, modern software languages and frameworks for fullstack development such as javascript, python, react, redux, flask, express, postgresql, SQLAlchemy,

College UCLA 2011-2016

• Art History Major-took classes in advanced math such as linear algebra, multivariable calculus